let questions = [
  {
    heroImage: 'question1',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>The person applying a tourniquet is at a low risk of contracting a disease from the victim’s blood.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. The risk of contamination by the victim’s blood is very low. In fact, the risk of contracting HIV from infected blood coming into contact with non-intact skin (such as scrapes and lacerations) is less than 0.1%. There is no risk of contracting HIV if infected blood comes into contact with intact skin. (Source: <a href="http://www.cdc.gov/hai/pdfs/bbp/exp_to_blood.pdf" target="_blank">CDC</a>)</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question2',
    answer: 'Fiction',
    question:
      '<p>Tourniquets are unsafe: they cause serious injury to the limb and infections.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>That is Fiction. Tourniquet use usually does not result in complications for the limb. A <a class="mobilize-link" href="http://www.dtic.mil/cgi-bin/GetTRDoc?AD=ADA480277" target="_blank">study</a> conducted on 232 patients during the War in Iraq found no association between the length of time a tourniquet is used and possible complications like blood clots and amputation. The study also found that “no amputations resulted solely from tourniquet use.” (Source: Kragh JF, Walters TJ, Baer DG, et al. Practical use of emergency tourniquets to stop bleeding in major limb trauma. J Trauma. 2008;64:S38-49.)</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question3',
    answer: 'Fiction',
    question: '<p>Tourniquets should always be used as a last resort.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>That is Fiction. For serious bleeding of the arms or legs, tourniquets are the first line of therapy. Tourniquets are a safe and effective method of treating bleeding. Our experience over the past decade of conflict in the Middle East has shown this to be the case. In fact, universal tourniquet training, along with other methods of bleeding control, <a class="mobilize-link" href="http://archsurg.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=1107258" target="_blank">helped contribute to a death rate of just 3% for survivable injuries in the 75th Army Ranger regiment from 2001 to 2010</a>. The death rate in other parts of the military with no such universal training was around 24%.</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question4',
    answer: 'Fiction',
    question:
      '<p>Only trained medical professionals can apply tourniquets.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>That is Fiction. Laypeople can apply tourniquets. In fact, a recent study found that 89% of patients brought into selected trauma centers had tourniquets properly applied to control their bleeding. This study was the largest evaluation of prehospital tourniquet use in civilian population to date and concluded that tourniquets were applied safely and effectively by laypeople (Source: Schroll R, Smith A, McSwain NE Jr, et al. A multi-institutional analysis of prehospital tourniquet use. J Trauma Acute Care Surg. 2015;79(1):10-14.)</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question5',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>The U.S. military uses tourniquets to save the lives of troops</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. The U.S. military expanded its use of the tourniquet since the early 2000s and the beginning of the wars in Afghanistan and Iraq. The military now supplies each soldier with a tourniquet in their individual first aid kits. (Source: Goolsby, C., Branting, A., Chen, E., Mack, E., &amp; Olsen, C. (2015). Just-in-Time to save lives: a pilot study of layperson tourniquet application. Academic Emergency Medicine, 22, 1113-1117.)</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question6',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>Tourniquets should only be used for serious bleeding that is life threatening.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. Non-serious bleeding sometimes resolves on its own (i.e., it clots). Sometimes it requires direct pressure. For example, a small paper cut will probably resolve on its own and clot. On the other hand, if you cut yourself while cooking, you might need to apply direct pressure to the cut to get it to stop bleeding. </p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question7',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>You should tighten the tourniquet by twisting the rod until you literally cannot twist it anymore and the bleeding stops – even if it hurts the injured person.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. Twist the rod until all bleeding stops. You will likely need to twist it until you cannot twist anymore. This step may be painful for the injured person. Keep twisting until the bleeding stops.</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question8',
    answer: 'Fiction',
    question:
      '<p>You should loosen the tourniquet temporarily to give the injured person relief, then tighten it again.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>That is Fiction. Leave the tourniquet on until medical professionals arrive. Comfort the injured person, but do not loosen the tourniquet. Loosening the tourniquet could restart the bleeding. </p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question9',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>Put the tourniquet above the wound so that it is between the torso and the wound.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. First, place the tourniquet on the injured limb above the wound. “Above” means that it should be closer to the torso. Do not place the tourniquet on top of the wound.</p>'
  },
  {
    heroImage: 'question10',
    answer: 'Fact',
    question:
      '<p>If you are alone with somebody who has serious bleeding, you should apply a tourniquet first, and then call 911 for help.</p>',
    feedback:
      '<p>The correct answer is Fact. A serious bleed leaves a victim with only a small window of time before they face potential death. If you are by yourself, stop the bleeding first, and then try to get help. If you are with others, then direct someone to call 911 as a first step and then stop the bleeding.</p>'
  }
];

export default questions;
